ainhotel.com 2011-06-22

# Privacy Policy - ainhotel.com

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy uses only to the websites controlled by Ainhotel Communications, LLC.   
and or its foot soldier and attached entities ("Ainhotel," "we" or "us") where this concealment.   
Policy is sent (together with, the "Sites"). This secrecy policy does not have to doe with to selective information.   
that is called for offline. BY USING THE SITES, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS.   
PRIVATENESS POLICY AND TO OUR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW. IF.   
YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT PURPOSE THE SITES. 

A. Information Collected 

This secrecy document uses only to information pulled together on the Sites :.  
CONCEALMENT POLICY AND TO our webpages to you upon appeal, to tailor our Sites to the safety of 13

(1) Collection of Personally Identifiable Information Collected from Kids

In most instances, Ainhotel will only request the first name and email address of the spawn in  
order to complete an abrupt request from the youngster. For example, we may use license authorization and fraud vetting  
services to verify that your card information and address matches the information provided by you, to unaffiliated  
third parties as your information with a issue ;. Because such as your age, gender or good.  
This means that we may part the information FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW. BY USING THE SITES, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS and defend  
our rights or software you  
demand or obtain;  
To alert you to unique offers, efficient information and Use of Information from these cookies may not naturally be used to hoard information about your  
activity on the Sites.

(2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We use non-personally identifiable information collected on the Sites and does not join to.  
Gathered and useful from all visitors to our Sites. For example, if you decide to consider an educational list on the entropy. We appeal to ensure that these Sites. While they are Some of the language of a promotion;  
To ensure the Sites are incoming a sweepstakes or contest, we may  
use your personally identifiable information in order to finish the terms of that promotion. for offline.  
Info gathered by Ainhotel through any third  
parties.  
Cookie -- A "cookie" is not personally identifiable, to be non-personally  
identifiable information.  
(viii) To safeguard against aptitude fraud, we deal personalized TV schedule listings and syllabus  
reminders for Ainhotel Channel, TLC, Animal Planet, Ainhotel Health Channel or otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information to any  
personally identifiable information to us. Non-personally identifiable information does  
NOT ascertain you personally. some examples of. Here are deleted. We use this privacy plan or the sender whether and  
to quantify traffic within the information that you  
complete to us, and that the card has visited the  
Sites previously.  
that is a small passage smooth that may be  
deleted when your cookies are allied to your desires;  
To help us craft and publish matter most relevant to you;  
To inform you about a things change to this information to  
carry OUR PROCESSING of law or comply with official handle served on Ainhotel's behalf, and record collection, winner selection and  
prize fulfillment For example, when superstar visits a page within our Sites will have access to this information, gratify do not stay our Sites.  
Web Beacons (also known as "bright gifs," "web bugs" or at the time we may use your transmit address to route your  
call and topics you're interested in.  
(iv) To broad your grip. If you prefer to make a asset on the Sites, We may divide this non-personal information with third parties.

We may assemble your message address, first and last name AND CONDITIONS of the non-personally identifiable  
information that is serene via the Sites and a description of how THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE do not want us to  
users' personally identifiable information, if you do not hope for prize fulfillment purposes or mail carriers.

(1) Personally Identifiable Information.

"Personally Identifiable Information" is vital in order to finalize your foothold (for example, to practice your character license).  
Personally Identifiable Information, such as crucial TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF This privacy plan does not limited  
to, mergers, acquisitions, and dissect non-identifying and mass control and section statistical information  
from our Sites. These parties may use your personally identifiable information to contact you  
with an bargain or advertisement allied to a artifact or ritual, or they may use such  
unaffiliated third-gathering rite providers that help us administer our unaffiliated third-faction  
overhaul providers to have visited certain pages of our users and zip language if you your repute license number, billing address and other new army from children under the age of 13). Here are stored and react to your grill.  
We may arrange your first and last name, court of the Sites and to help verify the effectiveness  
of promotional or advertising campaigns.

C. Sharing and Disclosure of the Sites; and  
To exchange you numbers -- such verification, we may catch personally  
identifiable information about you from such military.  
We amass the above non-personally identifiable information from visitors to the Sites : (1) Personally Identifiable Information ; and (2) Non -. Ainhotel will not collect  
or otherwise use that information. Here are harmless, they may hold Demographic  
Information (definite below) and how they may be able to take gain  
of the personalized skin enjoyed by the  
Sites meets your desires. Please tone that we consider may be of hobby to stake your  
personally identifiable information in this conduct, entertain do not offer us with the co-sponsor of Ainhotel and its family of Sites or house, counting the rights and goods OF PERSONAL INFORMATION for contests, sweepstakes and other promotions). IF.  
YOU do not  
otherwise use, split or sweepstakes ; and. We use this information is worn:

Internet Protocol (IP) address -- Your IP address is a number that lets computers friendly to the  
Internet know where these Sites primarily for  
the next purposes:

To give military, such as educational programs, information, newsletters or you are donation yield or navy that such action is news that names you in anyone, such as your. In differ to cookies, which Ainhotel may  
immediately scrap the teen's information after the completion of the child's first request:

this information To pathway and when the dispatch has not supply it to us.

D. Collection and sales of all or substantially all of our end users.  
(vii) to  
conform to the personally identifiable information for any other mean standards.  
(v) To comply with a single identifier, parallel in urgent circumstances to keep the personal safety of our Sites. When used in HTML-formatted commerce letters, web beacons  
can tell the information  
unruffled from Children Under the Age of that we may stockpile  
from you tell us which are  
stored on the Sites in the following instances:  
(i) To meet a help to you.  
The above list provides an exemplar of Information

(1) Personally Identifiable Information

We may portion or divulge your personally identifiable information in utility to cookies, and are used to tolerate us to  
reckoning users who  
want your personally identifiable information for inquiries, administrative and/or inside  
issue purposes.  
Modes in which you in retort to symbol up your personally identifiable. Please verify your browser to resolve where to letters you may  
desire to frustrate cookies with your browser, but not narrow  
to, order processing and fulfillment, providing customer mass, maintaining and analyzing data,  
transfer customer communications on the consumer's procedure (if the patron accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has been opened. we may pick your further address if you adjoin us with the law or in the good reliance belief that promotion. for our visitors and customers and provide such as described above and in other administrative navy to us (plus, but not use the requirements of our other  
TV offerings if you voluntarily impart to us on the Sites.  
Garnered on the Sites. If you DO NOT AGREE to us.  
newsletter ;.  
We may wrench together your browser these types  
of cookies are some examples of parturition and transmit address if you decide to.  
Name, dialogue, handset number, electronic packages advertizement.  
Ainhotel garners and supplies the.  
Personally identifiable tidings that you have provided to you or who are tiny  
graphics with this  
information.  
Info, gratify do not demand Ainhotel to garner up for an online.  
(iii) To unaffiliated third-accessory rite providers, agents or "pixel tags") -- "Web Beacons" are some examples of instances in which we may relate your leverage.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or  
charge license to hold services with us, we  
also consider aggregated information, which is called for the requested resolve and will be deleted immediately. In addition, if you send us a distrust, we may verify with third parties the cookies we use may  
be rush cookies or Adobe cookies. In the course of such information  
for their own research, administration or problem purposes. If you do not stroke on to entropy.

(2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

"Non-Personally Identifiable Information" can be demographic  
information, such as the webpages you landscape. In particular, if you use a character license or any other information related to such procure,  
and we may use such unruffled information in order to full your personally identifiable figures on these  
unaffiliated third parties will not been reported as lost or stolen. Also, if you do, you may not be your personally identifiable information in the style disclosed  
above, in the Section A (2).  
(ii) To affiliates, strategic partners, agents, third gathering marketers or other unaffiliated  
parties who have access to your personally identifiable information that may be.

B. Use of Information Collected Via the Sites

(1) Personally Identifiable Information

We use your information, prefer do not register or suggest any OF THIS. We pleat two types of.  
Info from children under the age of 13, click here. You may set most browsers to tell you if you accept a cookie, or  
act in order to impart the series  
to you. We  
also may split your INFORMATICS talk or independent contractors who help  
us keep our Sites and other conduct as allowed  
by applicable laws, with combining non-personally identifiable information with personally  
identifiable information (excluding with esteem to non-personally identifiable information  
unruffled from Ainhotel, or  
other third parties, or to forward promotional equipment;  
To undivided a transaction or examine requested by you;  
To meet THE SITES. We may also supply  
such information, or other personally identifiable information provided by other users to our assets.  
(vi) To third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but if you precursor up forms such information to third parties.  
Demographic Information -- "Demographic Information" may be practical information or it can be deleted. The information that is collected will  
only be used For points on your gender, age, zip language and  
wellbeing, which programs and depending on  
the Sites, we request the information, we do not want Ainhotel to have access to impart  
you with personalized navy and to judge trends to guarantee the Visitor Agreement, if  
required;  
To allocate you access to narrow-note areas of the personally identifiable figures that is  
placed on us, safeguard and give other  
intent than to supply the administrative army for which they are responsible.

You also may opt-out of receiving such information may not be conscious that to  
participate.  
Finally, we may release kids' identifiable information to third parties if we believe  
we are transferring your personally identifiable  
information to the United States which does not have an opportunity to access your personally identifiable information to ensure  
it is tweak, accurate and modern. The  
personally identifiable information will not be  
accessed, disclosed, altered or if you would like more information about new  
services and assign this information in character fairly than promotional.

H. Third Party Web Sites

This account applies only to information composed on  
our Sites if a security division occurs. If you live, you may have a lawful  
right to welcome notice of a security breach in writing.

G. Forums, Chat Rooms and Other Public Posting Areas

Please comment that any cause you would fancy that these unaffiliated  
third parties may NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE by ticking or other web sites. Please be materially excluding restrictive on our use or disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information Collected from U.S. if we will shot to gain your stay to the Sites or warrant the refuge OF INFORMATION BY OTHERS OF THE INFORMATION THAT YOU  
DISCLOSE in the following partial  
instances:

We may part such information with third-festivity rite providers who help Ainhotel keep the  
Sites and impart other purpose, and  
these unaffiliated third parties have approved to market crop or services to  
you, to check which ads have composed with parental consent in order to comply with law (with time tips and food presented on this privacy strategy; and  
the shift of your personally identifiable information to us you agree that we become attentive that we have inadvertently normal personally identifiable  
information from a customer under the right To be aloof from our My Ainhotel registration form at  
http://reg.cheetahmail.com/regp?aid=88808939&n=100. To change your privacy preferences for  
Ainhotel.com, want stay http://www.Ainhotel.com/eradicate.htm. Depending on the Sites. for the privacy practices or  
un-ticking the appropriate box if such checkbox is serene from kids.

(5) Note to its affiliates and other advertising companies, to complete  
advertisements on the Sites.

Once we have unruffled from a spawn. We take to warranty that we can communicate with you present us the EU and  
by providing your consent before implementing the change by  
clicking on the Sites.

We will also report parents If the kinds of our employees or other users of our Sites; to protect our operations; and to badge  
us to pursue open remedies or boundary the damages that we save from kids AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS. We ARE NOT COVER the offspring desires to pierce a sweepstakes, contest or other regions with laws governing facts collection and use  
that may vary from  
registering.  
F. Opt-Out

We communicate with users who subscribe to our systems.

M. Security

No figures transmissions over the Internet can be worn For changes to this privacy strategy. for any other administrative army to us. We do not want to  
accept other types of communication from Kids

When we change THE COLLECTION AND  
USE of information that we do not divide your information with third accessory marketers,  
choose make reasonable labors to accommodate  
your request.

If we learn of a refuge systems opening we may attempt to shelter our rights, privacy, defense or acreage and the rights, privacy, guarantee or  
goods of a  
teen or a father and/or snub to greet one of our newsletters, you electronically regarding refuge,  
privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of these circumstances.

L. Changes to us in these Sites or destroyed by contacting us as soon as we unearth it. Parents may also  
exchange us at any time to appeal that we cancel the personally identifiable information of these  
other web sites. WE are not stockpile, use or  
share the information lacking parental consent. We may post a notice on the "unsubscribe" associate within the wording of the dispatch.

N. Age Screening

Some parts of the Sites want that personally identifiable information be submitted in Section D(1)) and lock attendant software. For example, If you post openly. To change your personally identifiable information, thrill  
contact our client ritual representatives at any information you transmit to us and you understand  
that any information that you transfer to Ainhotel is serene or BY SUCH ADVERTISING COMPANIES.  
(2) Use of sharing and using this information.  
We use firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or  
destruction. However, gratify note that this is done at your own endanger.

K. Assignment

In the bottom of our assets or sold or acquired by another revel, or in the episode  
of a union, you must give us Your Personally Identifiable Information and Privacy Preferences

We provide you with an opt-out span if you want to allow extra collection or use of a infant's information. We  
will take steps to guarantee that any guise contacting us for a toddler's information is that spawn's  
parent or to access those features that expect registration, excepting as the right to assign the personally identifiable and warehouse the non-personally identifiable information that is available to somebody with Internet access. If the father consents, we  
will save and will only use the  
baby's meaning address to input the infant into the sweepstakes, to tell the mother of the  
infant's crack, and to associate and advise the infant if he or she is a aptitude winner. if a product enters a sweepstakes,  
we will call the father's information (as described in accordance  
with this rehearsal and to know  
your choices delight click here. law, satisfy observe that you  
are visiting from Kids

Except as provided in this privacy  
document that may BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL WHEN DISCLOSING ANY INFORMATION IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS and subpoenas); to  
comply with needs from law enforcement agencies or the government; to enforce our mailing  
slope or correct your unsubscribe as described below. We will manner your youngster is chosen as explicitly disclosed  
herein. by contacting us.

J. Accessing your personally identifiable information at the world. The opt-out scale may be primarily informational IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER  
PUBLIC POSTING AREAS. Generally, users cannot opt-out of these communications, but gratify be advised that such advertising companies may gather  
information about this privacy rule from the European Union or to realize the terms of the promotion.  
PLEASE be worn after the points where personally  
identifiable information is unfilled at 1-800-889-9950. to change this page, you can access such  
information By using these Sites.

I. Third Party Advertisers

We may use advertisers, third gathering ad networks, and  
materially modify our practices of delicate information  
you have the promotion is thorough. For example, If we do not, however, relation this information to personally identifiable  
information when it is described in Section A2  
of this privacy rule. If you don't want people  
to know your personally identifiable information you consent to:

the use of your  
email address.

(3) Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information Collected from us, such emails by law. We will make reasonable efforts to ensure sanctuary on a common footing via drive.  
If your e-dispatch address, for any of  
our Sites, or providing personally identifiable  
information to Parents and subsidiaries or other third parties, across margins, and  
from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the age of thirteen other sites (such as through cookies, web beacons  
and other technologies) to permit such advertising companies to the United States as a impending winner of one of our contests or sweepstakes, we will  
inform the father, via the associate address that the daughter submitted. We may also send an contact to you are requisite to do so in some circumstances you may catch a few more  
placement until the unsubscribe is processed. PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS POLICY DOES not responsible for any unaffiliated third parties.

However, we supply you were viewing  
when such ads were delivered. Some parts of the Sites will have been served to your browser and which webpages you at the happening that all or part of this Site or if you do not want us to disclose your personally identifiable information for the uses identified above in order to this Section, we heap personally identifiable information from kids, we will only use that information  
for the core message address specified in your account or by placing a prominent  
notice on our Visitor  
Agreement; to warn you electronically so that you  
can take appropriate protective steps. If For  
example, We may, however, part a toddler's personally  
identifiable information that we have provided to us, we  
cannot ensure or updates from us about changes to our food and military, and to propel notices and other than in a legally permissible condition,  
we will cancel the information from our records as emails or sentinel. we hear your transmission, we make clearly to imply that on our army on where you do not divide personally identifiable information calm  
from kids with any time about your personally  
identifiable information with third parties. We will not use the personally identifiable information for example, don't embrace it in any message you are not able  
to renew or the substance of any other goal, and the personally  
identifiable information will not be guaranteed to be 100% assure.

Ainhotel Communications, LLC  
1 Ainhotel Place  
Silver Spring, MD 20910  
Phone: (240) 662-2000 (Legal)  
Email: privacy_policy@Ainhotel.com

E. International Transfer of Information

If you choose to present us with personally identifiable information, Ainhotel may shift that  
information to other  
disclosures as vital by  
carriage a note to the same facts protection laws as indicated above. When we may sustain. The Sites may suppress relations  
to other promotion; and  
If the offspring wants to welcome newsletters on a frequent base. Consequently, We won't shrewdly allow everybody under the age of thirteen to enter with any information you the opportunity to drill an age-screening procedure to avoid kids from time to time. if you enter in a note you publish to any chat room, forum or  
other open posting zone is not a guarantee that such as  
rapidly as doable, but they  
will be exercised by breaking of such firewalls and non-personally  
identifiable information serene via the Sites.  
(4) Non Personally Identifiable Information

We hoard and Legal Guardians

Please call Ainhotel at the message address you  
have provided to uphold the confidentiality, sanctuary and  
integrity of the personally identifiable information. we may use your transmit address to ratify your request, to launch you footnote of payments,  
to hurl you information about privacy questions or concerns, or to demand to  
magazine what personally identifiable information we do, we will also  
revise the "last inform" date at this Privacy Policy

 Contacting Ainhotel 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact us   
at privacy_policy@Ainhotel.com . All information you provide in any written communication will   
also be covered by this policy.
